[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the largest of the Canary Islands.", "correct_answer": "Tenerife", "incorrect_answers": ["Gran Canaria", "La Palma", "Montana Clara"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following modern diseases evolved as a protection against malaria?", "correct_answer": "Sickle Cell Anemia", "incorrect_answers": ["Asthma", "Lactose Intolerance", "Tay Sachs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the 1939 version of The Four Feathers which starred Ralph Richardson, C. Aubrey Smith, and John Clements?", "correct_answer": "Michael Korda", "incorrect_answers": ["William Wellman", "Billy Wilder", "Henry Faversham"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the church in which the boys in the movie Sleepers spent a lot of time as kids?", "correct_answer": "Holy Angels", "incorrect_answers": ["Holy Child", "St. Anthony", "Our Lady Of  Perpetual sorrows"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Fast Times at Ridgemont High, character Jeff Spicoli rescues Brooke Shields from drowning and blows the reward money, hiring which band to play at his birthday party?", "correct_answer": "Van Halen", "incorrect_answers": ["KISS", "Blue Oyster Cult", "Cheap Trick"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cockroaches are among the most resilient creatures on our planet. But how long can they survive without air?", "correct_answer": "45 minutes", "incorrect_answers": ["60 minutes", "10 minutes", "2 hours"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Wedding Crashers, when Jeremy called out hot route, John ran the hot route and tackled Clair when she caught the interception.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 2003 drama film directed by Bernardo Bertolucci is based on Gilbert Adairs novel The Holy Innocents?", "correct_answer": "The Dreamers", "incorrect_answers": ["La Luna", "II Canale", "The Sheltering Sky"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Saturn has more then 80 known moons.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the winner of the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Picture for 1988.", "correct_answer": "Cocktail", "incorrect_answers": ["Hot to Trot", "Caddyshack II", "Rambo III"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the maximum angle of field of vision compound eyes can have?", "correct_answer": "360 degrees", "incorrect_answers": ["290 degrees", "310 degrees", "200 degrees"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This artificial island, whose name literally means Pepper Islet, is part of the Oresund Bridge, connecting Denmark with Sweden.", "correct_answer": "Peberholm", "incorrect_answers": ["Kansai", "Flakfortet", "Palm Islands"]}]